A real horror story…
The Night Stalker is a mystery, horror, thriller
film directed by John Llewellyn Moxey.
Wisecracking reporter Carl Kolchak investigates a string of murders
in Las Vegas and suspects the culprit is a vampire.
His editor thinks he's crazy and the police think he's a
nuisance, so Kolchak takes matters into his own hands.
Carl Kolchak, played by Darren McGavin.
Gail Foster, played by Carol Lynley.
Tony Vincenzo, played by Simon Oakland.
Bernie Jenks, played by Ralph Meeker.
Sheriff Warren A. Butcher, played by Claude Akins.
Police Chief Ed Masterson, played by Charles McGraw.
The Night Stalker is an American made-for-television horror film which aired
on ABC on January 11, 1972, as their ABC Movie of the Week.
In the film, Carl Kolchak (Darren McGavin), an investigative reporter, comes to
suspect that a serial killer in the Las Vegas area is actually a vampire.
The Night Stalker set a record for the most viewed made-for-TV film.
It was followed by a sequel, The Night Strangler, and a television series, Kolchak: The
Night Stalker, both of which had McGavin reprise his role as Carl Kolchak.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.